I was born to be an idol.
I was told by my parents that I was born to be an idol.
What a Cinderella story!
I'd like to try diving overseas.
A little bit the same.
I've never seen it before.
You've never heard of a flog rider?
There's so many of them.
A place to go?
Oh, my God, I can't believe I'm in a place like this.
The members have become so interesting.
I wanted to be here.
I feel like I'm still doing it.
That's great.
Now, let's continue.
This way.
I'm curious.
Here we go.
Who thought he was the only one who could do it
Who thought he was the only one who could do it.
You know, like in school...
I can't compete with his ability to cry.
Or his ability to recoil
I've never thought about fighting.
That's really interesting.
I see.
I've even thought about standing on the same field in the first place.
That's interesting.
Yeah, it is.
I don't think so.
It's not that I don't think so. I mean, you wrote in school that you're smart.
It's like, "Wow, that's great.
I think so, but...
I've given up on that.
That's great.
That's not how I pictured it.
When I hear you talk about him.
You seem really smart.
And you seem really athletic.
He's a high-spec person.
Someone who's willing to work really hard.
He'll do his best in everything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not at all.
But there's no one in school who can compete.
That's why you become an idol.
I guess so.
A-Land
There's a lot of them.
You want to fight?
I don't want to fight.
They seem peaceful.
I don't think so.
I don't really like fighting.
You fought a lot in The Last Idol.
Out in the open.
That was a super fight.
I thought it was great.
There were a lot of fights during the show.
Yes, there were.
I'm a pacifist, but I tried.
I'm not too sure I want to...
If I compare myself...
I start to think I'm lower and lower.
But...
I know...
I think that idols
From a comprehensive point of view
The manager...
I've never seen anyone like him before.
I've ever met.
He's an adult, of course.
I mean, he's a very good adult.
But he's got that eternal childlike spirit.
He's got a child's heart and a sense of humor.
And yet, of course, you're doing your job.
I'm impressed.
I've always been a very serious person.
All my life.
But your manager...
I don't think of him as a serious person.
I don't think of myself as a serious person.
That's what inspired me.
I've learned that it's okay to live like this
I've heard a lot of stories
I heard many stories from the past
I've got a lot of ideas.
And ideas.
I'm impressed.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I admire the most.
My manager.
Elementary, middle school, high school...
Nearly uninterrupted, uninterrupted, uninterrupted.
Nearly unexcused absences.
Never absent, never absent, never absent.
Yeah.
I thought that was really great.And I thought that was really great.
I'm sure.
It was just the echo one.
I've seen the manager's yearbook.
I've seen the correspondence slips and stuff.
I've seen your grades.
Zero.
It's normal.
Even if you don't do these activities.
I had a fever.
I had to take some time off.
You know, high school students...
Zero.
I think that's really
I think it's the power of humanity.
Going to the same place every day.
That's a lot of work.
I don't know.
I'm amazed that you were able to do it so effortlessly.
It's amazing.
You're so healthy.
That's amazing.
I've never seen you sick outside for two days.
Ansovia Lampen, located on the 4th floor of Invenz
All-you-can-eat and all-you-can-drink prezzie for 90,3,200 yen.
All-you-can-eat and all-you-can-drink prezzie for only 3,200 yen for 90 minutes!
Over 30 kinds of food ingredients can all be refilled!
Over 60 kinds of drinks are also available for free!
For customers with reservations
Cheese Kimbap as a gift as a reservation!
Please visit us at Ansovia Lampen on the 4th floor of Invens!
Let's continue!
This is a question from me to Nanami.
I've written two.
The first one is.
How did you get started with idols?
The reason why I started idoling...
My parents love idols.
I liked Morning Musume。 I was influenced by them and I've always liked them.
I was influenced by them, and I've always liked them.
When I was 3 years old
entertainment office when I was 3 years old.
I found a flyer and went to an entertainment office.
My mom told me to take it.
So I decided to take it.
I felt like I came in like I was learning to dance.
But then I came out of there.
I've been in idol groups since I was 3 years old.
I've been in some kind of group since I was 3 years old.
You've been an idol since you were 3?
Well, not really an idol.
I wasn't very good with the microphone.
But I danced in a lot of events.
Oh, wow.
You've been out in the public eye.
I was old!
I was a very senior dancer.
So I've been doing it for a long time.
And the next thing I knew, I was an idol.
So I joined an office.
I joined a group.
And then the group started going to idol festivals and stuff.
Wow, that's amazing.
So when I found out I was an idol...
That's great, because 3 years old doesn't have many characters.
That's right.
So, you know, when I got older.
I didn't want to be an idol.
You didn't want to be an idol.
In that kind of environment...
I thought I had no choice but to be an idol.
It was my destiny.
Wow.
My parents told me that I was born to be an idol.
I was told by my parents that I was born to be an idol.
What a Cinderella story!
It's too amazing.
I've heard of little girls...
"I was born to be an idol.
What?
That's amazing!
Nice parents.
It's just a normal conversation.
They said something like that.
Wow, I'd love to be told something like that.
And then I auditioned for Ori Ori Ori and changed the name of the group.
And they changed the name of the group.
It's like it's just been going on and on and on.
I see.
So you've been an idol since you were born.
You've been an idol since right here.
Wow, that's amazing.
But even now...
Your feelings for your idols...
You haven't cooled down.
It's like you've been an idol since birth.
Always.
Other idols?
But I get bored easily.
Really?Really?
I get bored.
It's easy for my enthusiasm to wane.
But I've always been an idol.
Wow, that's great.
Type B?
Type O.
Oh, I was wrong.
That's not even close.
Not even close.
Type O.
Okay, one more thing.
It's totally different.
If you were to be born again, would you be a man or a woman?
Which would it be?
I'd rather be a bird.
You said you wanted to be a bird?
I like heights. That's why I want to fly.
Have you tried skydiving?
I'd like to.
We're kind of on the same page.
I've never seen that before.
Have you ever tried it?
No, I haven't.
Have you?
100 meters, for real, twice.
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
That was fun.
Did you do that for a project?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was a project.
That's amazing.
Skydiving... that's what I want to do most right now.
I've been filming skydiving for about two years now.
I'm going to go skydiving.
Are you interested in paragliding?
I'm really interested.
I'll go.
It's amazing to be in a place like this.
Last one.
Okay.
I'll tell everyone.
This is so great, it's the reason I became an idol.
Oh, my God!
That's what I thought when I heard it!
We're the same! I thought!
You didn't talk to him about this?
No!
How did you become an idol?
I didn't really want to be an idol in the first place.
But my father and I were both very interested in the entertainment industry.
My father wanted to be a singer.
This is a funny story.
He wanted his daughter to become one.
I saw a flyer for the audition for Starlast.
In a magazine I was reading at the time.
The father happened to see it and said
He said, "There's no other way but to go for this audition.
So she auditioned.
So, at that time
When I sang
When I sang the song, my sister told me
She asked me if I wanted to join a group she was forming in Sendai.
But I wanted to be a solo artist, so I refused at first.
I said, "I want to work as a soloist, so I don't mind being an idol.
But after that, they asked me to come to the lessons anyway.
I started going to the lessons, and about three months later, they told me that I would be on stage.
That was the first time I was asked to perform on stage as Tohoku-san.
That was the first time I was suddenly on stage as Tohoku-san.
That was the first time I stood on stage as Tōhoku-san.
I didn't start idolizing of my own volition.
But the reason why I have been doing it all this time is because I started to enjoy it.
I have always liked to stand in front of people.
I also wanted to stay here forever, and I'm still doing it.
I wanted to stay here forever, and that's probably why I'm still doing it now.
So I didn't really want to be an idol.
How did it go?
I guess you could say that I just went with the flow.
But are you glad you did it?
I think so. I don't regret it at all.
The timing was good.
I think it was great timing.
Is everyone else in the group like that?
I don't think there were too many girls who said, "I want to be an idol.
I had a lot of them, and they all said they wanted to be models or actresses.
Many of them came to the agency saying they wanted to be models or actresses, and were kind of tricked into joining.
But the fact that all the members are continuing now.
But the fact that all the members are still doing it now means that they are doing it because they want to do it.
So I guess I've learned the joy of this idol business along the way.
I like that.
That's good.
How long have you been doing it?
Well, we've been doing it for six or seven years now, so it's been a long time.
So it's a good environment for everyone to be in.
Yeah.
Most of the members haven't changed that much.
So we've been together for a long time.
Maybe it's the slow synthesis that's good.
That's right.
You can't do it for 7 years if you're worried.
So what the heck.So what the heck.
Even though we're going through a lot of hard times
I think we get along well
I don't know about other groups
But I get the impression that you guys get along really well.
Really?
Even now, after a concert or an event.
We'll go out for dinner or something.
That's how I feel.
Secondly, if you weren't doing this, what would you want to be?
What? This is kind of the same thing!
Oh, wow!
I didn't do the high lattice. You were a normal person, right?
That's right.
I wanted to work part-time so badly.
But you know what?
I understand. I would love to work as a beer vendor at a baseball game or in the hospitality industry.
But what I want most is to be a professional baseball player.
You are really bad at sports.
Really?
I'm really bad at sports.
Surprisingly.
Yes, I am. I'm not used to it, but when I change my genes and become more athletic, I want to be a professional baseball player and hit super form runs.
That sounds great. That's a dream come true.
I'd like to win the championship, and then have a beer party at the end of the tournament.
That's right.
In the end, I might want to do something that involves interaction with people.
I guess so.
Thank you for your hard work.
After talking to you for the first time
She's totally different from my image.
I thought she's an interesting girl, a little different from other people.
But we have a lot in common.
We have a lot of things in common.
I think we're going to get along really well.
I want to go out to dinner with her.
I'd like to go out to dinner with her, and I'd like to fly with her.
I'm going to fly!
Thank you for your hard work.
Today was the first time for me to shoot for YouTube.
I was really nervous because it was my first time to shoot a YouTube interview, but the truth is
But Yuna-chan is really good at talking.
We have a lot in common.
I'm really shy.
I can't talk to people at all, but we're usually on the same wavelength.
I don't know if we're on the same wavelength.
I can talk a lot.
I don't think any of my fans have ever seen me talk like this.
I don't think they've ever seen me talking like this.
I'm talking with other people.
So I think they're really surprised.
I also had a lot of fun.
I want to go out for drinks with you.
I want to go sky-darling with you.
I'd like to get to know you better in the future.
The Sour & Beer Garden on the 4th floor of E-Beans
Sour & Beer Garden
The location was really nice.
The prechu deuke was really good too!
Please come and visit us!
Next time
In addition